- Defend a critical system.
Actually, you can say that basically very similar skills - are needed -
- For offensive and defensive cyber operations.
A defensive ability it is the -
- As we almost always use.
It's about monitoring -
- And discover intrusion into our systems.
Offensive cyber operations are about obtaining information -
–If the attacking system, or to make it difficult for the attacker -
- to use their systems, which in turn -
- is a defense measure, because it prevents these attacks.
The cyber defense is needed everywhere in the Armed Forces -
-And here we got the chance to deepen our knowledge a little -
- In how different associations work with their cyber defense.